A Finding Aid to the Gertrude Vanderbilt Whitney Papers, 1851-1975, bulk 1888-1942, in the Archives of American Art AAA.whitgert
Archives of American Art
- Journals, circa 1886-1939; Series 3; 2.5 Linear feet Boxes 9-12, 33
  - Personal Journals, circa 1886-1939; 3.1
    - Journal, Crossing the Atlantic from Liverpool to New York, circa 1886 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Journal (unbound), 1890 April 20-28 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Journal, "Across the Atlantic,", 1890 May (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Journal, Vol. I, 1890 May-September (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Journal, Vol. II, 1890 September-December (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Journal, Vol. IV, 1891 March-August (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Album, "Confessions", 1891-1894 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Diary, 1892-1893 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Impression Book, "People I Meet", 1893-1894 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Journal, "People", 1894 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Diary, 1894-1895 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Diary, Vol. II, 1895-1896 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Diary, Engagement to Harry Payne Whitney, 1896 April-August (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Journal Kept on Honeymoon, "My Trip Abroad", 1896-1897 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Journal, Vol. III, 1903-1905 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Journal, 1904-1911 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Art Journal, 1906-1907 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Journal, 1906 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - "My Motor Log Book", 1906-1924 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Journal, 1906 October 9-27 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - "A Line A Day" Book, 1907-1911 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Journal, circa 1908 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Journal, Paris, 1910-1911 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Flora Whitney's Journal, "Record of Plays Seen", 1910-1913 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Journal, circa 1912-1914 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Journal (unbound), 1918; 1913 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - "A Line A Day" Book, 1914 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Journals (2), Juilly Hospital, 1914 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Desk Diary, 1914 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Journal, Spain, 1920 September-October (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - "A Line A Day" Book, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Journal, Spain, 1928-1929 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Journal, Letter to "Dearest", 1930 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - "A Line A Day" Book, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Social Journals, 1893-1920; 3.2
    Journals are scanned in entirety.
    Journals are arranged chronologically.
    This subseries consists of dinner books (recording attendees and seating arrangements), a dance book (recording dances danced and with whom), an invitation book (listing people invited to different social gatherings), as well as bound and unbound volumes of invitations received and accepted, all of which document, to one extent or another, Gertrude Vanderbilt Whitney's various social activities and her social milieu.
    - "Dinner Book, Vol. I", 1893-1895 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - "Invitations Accepted" (unbound), circa 1893-1895 (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
    - "Dances", 1894-1896 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - "All Entertainment Book, Newport", 1895 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - "Dinner Book, Vol. II", 1895-1896 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - "Invitations" (unbound), before 1897 (Box 11, Folder 11-12)
    - "Dinners", 1899 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - "House Parties", 1905-1907 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - "Dinners", 1909-1910 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - "Invitations", 1914-1916 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Wedding Announcements and Invitations (loose), 1917-1920 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Invitations (loose), circa 1920s (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Oversize, "Dinners" scanned with Box 11, Folder 15, 1909-1910 (Box 33)
- Whitney Studio Club and Whitney Museum of American Art Files, 1921-1943; Series 4; 0.2 Linear feet Box 12
  This series consists of scattered material stemming from some of Gertrude Vanderbilt Whitney's art patronage activities and relating to the Whitney Studio Club, which opened in 1918 as an outgrowth of the Whitney Studio and the Friends of Young Artists, and the Whitney Museum of American Art, which opened in 1931 as an outgrowth of the Whitney Studio Club and the later Whitney Studio Galleries. Files include a sales and presentation notebook from the Whitney Studio Club listing works sold and/or presented to various institutions by Whitney, and catalogs, reports, a notebook (which appears to have been kept by Flora Whitney Miller), and writings from the Whitney Museum of American Art.
  The series has been scanned in its entirety.
  - Whitney Studio Club, Sales and Presentations, 1921-1926 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art (Box 12)
    - Catalogs, 1931-1942 (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
    - Coalition with Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1942-1943 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Financial Report, circa 1940 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Notebook (Kept by Flora Whitney Miller?), 1935-1942 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Writings by Lloyd Goodrich and Herbert More, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Sculpture Files, bulk 1909-1942; 1900-1960; Series 5; 3 Linear feet Boxes 12-15
  This series consists of files relating to Gertrude Vanderbilt Whitney's sculpture projects, including both proposed and completed commissions for various fountains, memorials and monuments. Projects that are especially well-documented include the Buffalo Bill Memorial, the Columbus Memorial, the Daughters of the American Revolution (D. A. R.) Memorial, the Foch National Memorial, the St. Nazaire Memorial, The Spirit of Flight (commissioned for the New York World's Fair in 1939 and erected permanently at LaGuardia Airport), and the Titanic Memorial. Also found are files for the donation and installation of the Vanderbilt Gates in Central Park and for an exhibition of sketches and models for the Victory Arch at the Whitney Studio Club, both in 1919. For the most part, files seem to have been part of those kept by the Whitney Museum of American Art. Files are primarily comprised of correspondence, contracts, printed material, notes, financial material, and other documentation.
  Material related to Whitney's sculpture projects can also be found amongst photographs and blueprints.
  The bulk of this series has been scanned; some news clippings and a Foch National Memorial, Inc., stamp have not been scanned.
  Sculpture files are arranged chronologically according to name of the project. Miscellaneous files are arranged at the end of the series.
  - Jeanne d'Arc Monument, 1916-1917 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Arlington Fountain (McGill University, Montreal, Canada), 1929-1933 (Box 12, Folder 10-12)
  - Aztec Fountain (Pan-American Building, Washington, D.C.), 1909-1911 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Buffalo Bill Memorial (Cody, Wyoming) (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1900; 1949; 1922-1942 (Box 12, Folder 14-15)
    - Cost Accounting, 1924 (Box 12, Folder 16-17)
    - General, 1924-1925 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      Oversized material housed in OV 44
    - Printed Material, undated; 1951 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Anton Cermark Memorial, circa 1934 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Columbus Memorial (Port of Palos, Spain) (Box 12)
    - General, 1926-1929 (Box 12, Folder 21-23)
    - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1927 January-February (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1927 March-May (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1927 June-July (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1927 July (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1927 August (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1927 August-September (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1927 September-December (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1930-1932 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, 1932-1935 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, Letters from Diplomats and Ambassadors, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 36-38)
    - Clippings, 1927-1929 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Printed Material, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Miscellany, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - D.A.R. Memorial (Box 13)
    - General, 1927-1929; 1938 (Box 13, Folder 4-5)
    - Correspondence, 1924-1930 (Box 13, Folder 6-8)
    - Financial Material, 1928-1929 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Clippings, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Jane A. Delano Memorial (American Red Cross), 1923-1927 (Box 13, Folder 11-12)
  - El Dorado Fountain (Pan-Pacific International Exposition), 1942; 1913-1917 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - First Division Memorial, 1920-1921 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Foch National Memorial (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 1928-1929 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1930 January-February (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1930 February (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1930 March (Box 13, Folder 18-19)
    - Correspondence, 1930 April (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1930 May (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1930 June-Septmember (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1930 October (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1930 November-December (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1933-1937 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Dinner Honoring Gertrude Vanderbilt Whitney, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Notebook of Responses to Invitations for Dinner Honoring Messrs. Coste and Bellonte, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Notebook, "Foch National Memorial, Inc.", 1929-1932 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Financial Material, 1931-1933 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Clippings, 1930-1932 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Printed Material, 1929-1932 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Foch National Memorial, Inc. Stamp, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Fourth Division Memorial, 1921-1930 (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
  - Major Pierre Charles L'Enfant Memorial, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Charles Lindbergh Memorial, 1927-1930 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Naval Memorial, 1928-1929 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Panama-Roosevelt Memorial (Box 14)
    - General, 1928-1929 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1932 (Box 14, Folder 8-11)
    - Printed Material, 1926-1930 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Rumsey Memorial, 1936-1937 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - St. Luke's Hospital, 1939-1941 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - St. Nazaire Memorial (Box 14)
    - General, 1923-1924 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1924-1948 (Box 14, Folder 16-17)
    - Dedication, 1926 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Printed Material, 1947; undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Spirit of Flight (Box 14)
    - Contracts, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1938-1942 (Box 14, Folder 21-22)
    - Printed Material, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Springfield Memorial (104th Massachusetts Regiment), 1928-1933 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Peter Stuyvesant Statue (Stuyvesant Square), 1936-1942 (Box 14, Folder 25-26)
  - Peter Stuyvesant Statue (Curacao), 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Three Figure Fountain (Replica of Whitney Fountain, Lima, Peru), 1922-1924 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Titanic Memorial (Box 14)
    - Printed Material, 1929-1931 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Drawing, 1914 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1920; 1931 (Box 14, Folder 31-32)
    - Correspondence, Erecting the Memorial, 1924-1931 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Union Square Memorial Competition, 1926 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Mrs. Samuel J. Untermyer Memorial, 1925; 1943 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Vanderbilt Gates, 1935-1938 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Victory Arch, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Worcester War Memorial Competition, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Sculptures, 1914-1935 (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
  - Miscellaneous Notes on Sculptures and Exhibitions, circa 1916-1925 (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
  - Oversize Buffalo Bill Memorial scanned with Box 12, Folder 18 (Box OV 44)
  - Oversize, Titanic Memorial, Drawing scanned with Box 14, Folder 30, 1914 (Box OV 44)
- Philanthropy Files, bulk 1915-1920; 1902-1923; Series 6; 2 Linear feet Boxes 15-17
  This series consists of files relating to some of Gertrude Vanderbilt Whitney's philanthropic activities spanning from before to just after the First World War, including her donations to various charities (especially war relief organizations), her sponsorship of the American Ambulance Field Hospital in Juilly, France during the First World War, and her support of the Greenwich House Social Settlement. Files primarily consist of correspondence, minutes, reports, and printed material. Among the Juilly Hospital files can be found a book of patient stories and photographs presented to Whitney as memento or token of appreciation, photographs and snapshots (mostly unidentified), a photograph album, and a certificate of service.
  See Appendix for List of Correspondents from Series 6
  Series has been scanned in entirety, with the exception of some printed material.
  Appendix: List of Correspondents from Series 6
  A
  Aerial League of America
  Air Service Memorial Fund
  Alliance Francais
  Allied Theatrical and Motion Picture Team
  Alsace-Lorraine Society of America
  American Artists Mutual Aid Association
  American Bible Society
  American Committee for Relief for Devestated France in the Near East
  American Defense Society, Inc.
  American Flying Club
  American Free Milk and Relief for Italy, Inc.
  American Forestry Association
  American Friends of Musicians in France
  American Fund for French Wounded
  American Hospital in Nice, France
  American Institute of Social Science
  America International College
  American Legion
  American National Committee for Relief of Refugees in Russia
  American Poets' Ambulances in Italy
  American Red Plus
  American Red Star Animal Relief
  American Women's Hospitals in Europe
  American Women's Magazine
  Americanization Committee; New York State Woman Suffrage Party
  America's Tribute to Britain
  Art War Relief
  Association for the Alleviation for the Condition of Orphan Children
  Association to Promote Proper Housing for Girls
  B
  Babies Hospital of the City of New York
  Babies' Welfare Association
  Belgian Military Committee
  Belgian Scholarship Committee
  Bide-A-Wee Home, Association Inc.
  Big Sisters, Inc.
  Bird Club of Long Island
  Blind and Crippled Relief Fund for American Soldiers and Sailors
  Blind Men's Improvement Club of New York
  Boy Scouts of American
  Brearly League
  British American Relief Association
  British Canadian Recruiting Mission
  British Canadian Patriotic Fund
  British Great War Veterans of America, Inc.
  British Pictorial Service
  British War Relief Association, Inc.
  C
  Camp Fire Girls
  Camp Merritt Fund
  Camp Upton Community Hall
  Cathedral of St. John the Divine
  Catherine Breshkovsky Russian Relief Fund
  Chalif Normal School of Dancing
  Child Health Organization
  Children on the Frontier (French-American)
  Children's Hospitals of Luke
  Citizens Union of the City of New York
  City Club
  City History Club
  Civic Forum
  Clear Pool Camp
  Colony Club Ambulance Fund
  Committee for Men Blinded in Battle
  Committee for Relief in the Near East
  Committee of Mercy
  Committee on Colonial and National Art, Archaeological Institute of America
  Committee on the Military Ball
  Committee to Secure Rank for Nurses
  Community Playhouse, Newport
  Converence Committee on National Preparedness
  Conference of Charities and Correction
  Convalescent Relief Division, Bellvue Hospital
  D
  Diocoesan Missionary and Church Extension Society
  Domestic and Foreign Missionary Society
  Dover Patrol Fund
  Duryea War Relief
  E
  East Side House Settlement
  Educational Dramatic League
  Emergency Aid of Pennsylvania
  F
  Federal Board for Vocational Education
  Federation of Associations for Cripples
  Free Milk for France
  Freedom, Inc.
  French Bureau
  French Heroes Fund, including Lafayette Memorial Fund, Inc.
  French Institute in the United States
  French Tuberculous War Victims Fund
  French War Emergency Fund
  Friends of France
  Friends of National Bible Institute
  French Sailors Relief Committee
  Fund to Aid the Devastated Villages in France
  G
  Garnett Fresh Air Home
  General Committee on Army and Navy Chaplains
  General Wartime Commission of the Church
  Girl Scouts, Manhattan Council
  Greater New York Philanthropic Society
  H
  Hebrew Sheltering and Immigrant Aid Society of America
  Henry Street Settlement
  Hero Land (Allied Bazaar), under the auspices of League of Allies
  Historical Society of Nantucket, MA
  Historical Society of Newport, RI
  Home for Convalescent Babies
  Home for the Aged
  Hospital and House of Rest for Consumptives
  Hospital Under the Three Flags
  Humanitarian Duct and Magazine
  I
  Indian Rights Association
  Institute of Applied Christianity
  Italian War Relief Fund of America
  Italy America Society
  J
  Joffre Tribute Committee
  Junior American Guard
  Junior Homeprojects Works
  Junior League
  Junior Patriots of America
  K
  Kings College Hospital
  Knights of Columbus
  Kowaiga School for Colored Youth
  L
  Ladies Kennel Association
  Lady Beatty's War Relief Fund
  Laying-in-a-Hospital
  League for the Presentation for American Independence
  League of the Allies
  League of Catholics
  League of Foreign Born Citizens
  League of Nations
  League to Enforce Peace
  Le Salon
  Liberty Film Committee
  Liberty Loan Committee, 3rd, 4th, Fine Arts Liberty Loan Committee, Women's Liberty Loan Committee
  M
  Manhattan Eye, Ear and Throat Hospital
  Manhattan Maternity and Dispensary
  Maternity Center Association
  Mayor's Committee of Women on National Defence
  Militia of Mercy
  Museum of French Art
  Musicians Fund, Union Trust
  Music School Settlement
  N
  Nassau County Association, Inc.
  Nassau Hospital Association
  National Aeronautic Committee
  Natoinal Allied Relief Committee
  National Arts Club
  National Association of Audobon Society
  National Bible Institute
  National Child Welfare Association, Inc.
  National Committee on Prisons and Prison Labor
  National Council of Women (National Liberty Sing)
  National Emergency Relief Society
  National Historical Society
  National Institute of Social Services
  National Kindergarten Association
  National League of Women's Service
  National Patriotic Song Committee
  National Phonograph-Records Recruiting Corp.
  Navy League of the United States
  Navy Relief Society
  Neighborhood Association
  Neighborhood Playhouse
  Neighbors League of America
  Netherlands Symphony Orchestra of New York
  New York Anti-Vivisection Society
  New York Association for the Blind
  New York Bible Society
  New York Committee of After Care of Infantile Paralysis Cases
  New York Committee of the American Committee for Devastated France
  New York Dispensary
  New York Eye and Ear Infirmary
  New York Kindergarten Association
  New York Medical College and Hospital for Women
  New York Nursery and Child's Hospital
  New York Orthopaedic Dispensary and Hospital
  New York Probation and Protective Association
  New York Society for the Relief of the Ruptured and Crippled
  New York Special Aid Society
  New York Zoological Society
  O
  Orphan's Automobile Day Association of New York, Inc.
  Open Stair Dwelling Co.
  Our Dumb Friends League
  Our Sacred Duty League
  P
  Park Fetes
  Park Hospital and Training School
  People's Institute
  People's of America Society
  People's University Extension Society of New York
  Permanent Blind Relief War Fund for Soldiers and Sailors
  Pilgrim Tercentenary Memorial Fund
  Piper's Club
  Playground and Recreation Association of America
  Polish Victims Relief Fund
  Presbyterian Hospital
  Prison Assocation of New York
  Professional Classes War Relief of America
  Professional Women's League
  Prospect Hill Day Nursery
  Protestant Episcopal Church
  R
  Red Cross Christmas Seal Campaign
  Red Cross Roll Call
  Red Cross Shop
  Refugees in Russia
  Refugees Relief Fund
  Relief Committee for Greeks of Asia Minor
  Relief Fund for the Families of French Soldiers
  Richmond Hill House
  Riggs School, Inc.
  Rocky Mountain Club of New York
  Rose Sidgwick Memorial Fund
  Ross Studios, Home Making and Motherhood Training
  Roumanian Relief Committee of America
  Russian Balalaika Orchestra
  Russian Charity Society
  S
  Saint Ambrose Community Center
  Saint Andrew's Convalescent Hospital
  Saint Andrew's Hospital Coffee Stand Society
  Saint Bartholomew's Church
  Saint John's Guild
  Saint Joseph's Convent and School
  Saint Luke's Home for Aged Gentlewomen
  Saint Luke's Hospital
  Saint Mark's Hospital of New York City
  Saint Mary's Free Hospital for Children
  Salvation Army, War Work Campaign
  School of Mothercraft War Service
  Seamen's Church Institute
  Secours Franco-American
  Secours National
  Serbian Aid Fund
  Serbian Relief Commission of America
  Seward Park Rehabilitation Center
  Sheltering Arms
  Sick Children's Transfer Society
  Smith College Club
  Snow Hill Normal and Industrial Institute
  Society for Italian Women
  Society for Relief of Destitute Blind
  Society of American Singles
  Society of Lying-in-a-Hospital
  Society of the Friends of Music
  Society of the New York Hospital
  Stage Society
  State Charities Aid Association
  State Commission of Prisons in New York
  Stony Wold Sanitarium Corp.
  Sunshine Settlement, Inc.
  Sun Tobacco Fund
  T
  Tank Corps League
  Tenement House Committee
  Traveler's Aid Society
  Tribune Fresh Air Fund
  Trinity Church
  U
  Union des Arts
  Union Settlement
  United Building Fund Campaign
  United Committee on Christian Service for Relief in France and Belgium
  United Committee on War Temperance Activities in the Army and Navy
  United Hospital Fund
  United Neighborhood Houses of New York
  United Settlement Committee of Association of Neighborhood Workers
  United States Food Administration
  United States Junior Naval Reserve
  United States Naval Forces Operation in European Waters
  United War Work Campaign
  V
  Vacation Association, Inc.
  Valentine's Manual of Old New York
  Vassar College
  Visiting Nurse Service
  Vocational Committee of the Kips Bay Neighborhood Association
  Voluntary Parenthood League
  Volunteer Hospital
  Volunteers of American, Volunteer Fresh Air and Outing Work
  W
  Wadsworth-Upton Tobacco Fund
  War Department Commission on Training Camp Activities
  War Industries Board
  War Savings Metal Market
  West Side Day Nursery
  Woman's American Supply League
  Woman's Auxiliary for Navy Recruiting, Inc.
  Woman's Auxiliary of the French Hospital
  Woman's Land Army of American, Inc.
  Woman's Municipal League of New York
  Woman's Naval Service, Inc.
  Woman's Practical Law Association
  Woman's Prison Association
  Woman's Roosevelt Memorial Association
  Woman's Section of the Navy League of the United States
  Woman's League for Animals and Free Hospital
  Women's National Committee
  Woodcroft League of America
  World's Talent Foundation
  World's War Biographical Society
  Worker's Bureau
  Y
  Yale University Glee, Banic and Mandolin Clubs
  Yorkville Neighborhood Association
  Yorkville Protective League Committee
  YMCA, War Work Funds
  YWCA, War Work Funds
  - Charities and War Appeals (Box 15)
    - A, 1916-1920 (Box 15, Folder 6-9)
    - B, 1916-1920 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - C, 1915-1920 (Box 15, Folder 11-12)
    - D, 1916-1919 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - E, 1918-1921 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - F, 1915-1920 (Box 15, Folder 15-16)
      Partially scanned
    - G, 1917-1920 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - H, 1916-1920 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - I, 1916-1920 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - J, 1917-1919 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - K, 1917-1920 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - L, 1915-1920 (Box 15, Folder 22-23)
    - M, 1915-1920 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - N, 1915-1920 (Box 15, Folder 25-31)
    - O, 1916-1920 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - P, 1916-1920 (Box 15, Folder 33-34)
    - R, 1915-1919 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - S, 1915-1920 (Box 15, Folder 36-37)
    - S, 1915-1920 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
    - T, 1917-1919 (Box 16, Folder 3)